native-languages.org 2016-10-31

# Native Languages of the Americas Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Native Languages of the Americas. Here is our privacy policy for our visitors. 

Native Languages of the Americas does not collect or keep any information about visitors to our website. We do use Google Adsense to serve ads for our site, and Google does use cookies to collect information about your visit (NOT including personal information like your name, address, email address, or telephone number) in order to provide advertisements they think will be appropriate for you. If you would like more information about that practice and to know how to disable it if you prefer, please visit Google's page about it [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

If you choose to send us email or use one of the contact forms on our website, we will only use your email address for its intended purpose (responding to your letter.) We will not sell or give your email address to any lists and we will not publish it on our website. The only exception is if you send us a picture to post on our website for identification, in which case we will post your email address along with the picture so that people can respond to your query. If you want us to post a picture without any email address, just let us know and we will do so (although you won't receive any responses that way!) 

Finally, this privacy policy applies only to the two domains which belong to us (http://www.native-languages.org and http://www.bigorrin.org.) If you follow a link from our site to some other site, you will need to read their own privacy policy page to know what their policy is. We do not intentionally link to any sites that use spyware or disrespect people's privacy, but we can't guarantee other websites' behavior. 

Wado, miigwech, pilamaya ye, and thanks to all!  
Native Languages of the Americas   

Back to our [Native American language](http://www.native-languages.org/) homepage
